True charm
is not about pleasing,
but making a man crave you
yet not dare to touch.
When you get home,
use a paper bag
to cover your head,
leaving only your eyes exposed.
Stand in front of a mirror,
strip down,
and really take a good look at yourself.
I want you to know very clearly
the most charming part
of your body,
and then show it without reservation.
Ms. Guan,
here are the contracts
with the UK subsidiary from three years ago.
And,
here are flowers from Mr. Lin.
He's invited you
to lunch at noon.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Put it here.
You're welcome.
I should be thanking you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been framed.
Mr. Guan,
we both work for Mr. Lin.
You don't need to be so polite.
I won't bother you then.
You have work to do.
You played a crucial role
in settling this.
So,
what reward do you want?
I hope
you don't forget our promise.
Ah.
I think we need
a bit more time for the engagement.
Understood.
I think Ms. Wen
still has some reservations about me.
Time is the best catalyst.
She'll see your shining points.
Maybe
it's just a lack of interaction.
How about
we go back this weekend
and have dinner with her?
That's very thoughtful of you.
By the way,
I heard you're looking into
the dealings with
our overseas subsidiaries.
Yes.
For the company's IPO,
I need to thoroughly review
all past contracts
to avoid any historical issues.
Especially overseas,
where issues are most likely to arise.
With you here,
I'm relieved.
Come on.
Cheers.
What do you think Guan Tiantian
wants to do?
Maybe
she just wants to marry a rich man.
It's so real.
This profound pain
is not like an acting.
What do you mean?
Look at the things Su Wei sent.
The score of
the lesson of attacking the heart is excellent.
Especially
the sense of brokenness and alienation
is so real.
Even Su Wei thinks
it's not something
that can be deliberately imitated by training.
She shows an unusual avoidance
to specific topics,
such as
family,
past,
and accidents.
Even
physiological disgust.
A woman with a simple background
who just wants to marry a rich man
wouldn't deliberately cultivate
such a painful charm.
I think
she wants more than just to be Mrs. Lin.
It's
something deeper.
Lin Jiming,
the Lin Group,
or
something we almost forgot.
You mean...
Send someone to the UK
to investigate.
Keep a close eye on her.
From today on,
who she meets,
where she goes,
or
even her subtle expressions,
every move she makes,
must be reported to me.
I need to know every day.
Understood?
Yes.
Sir,
this is the case of Niudingshan's divorce.
I've uncovered some new evidence.
Please take a look.
The correlation
is not direct enough.
What about Bai Qiang?
She insists it's a marital dispute
and denies any fraud.
Jiang,
remember,
evidence and procedure
are our only weapons.
Okay, sir.
I'll keep investigating.
Son,
try this.
The cook made it all afternoon.
It's your favorite since childhood.
Thanks, mom.
Here.
Thank you.
Mom,
Tiantian is actually a good cook.
You can talk about cooking more.
You must be busy with work,
so you rarely cook, right?
I don't have time to cook fancy dishes,
but I can make some
simple home-cooked meals.
After all, I'm on my own,
so I need to take care of myself.
I'm quite envious of Jiming.
He can come home
and enjoy such delicious meals anytime.
He's lucky.
But he's
picky about food.
Oh,
really?
So you're picky, huh?
You always seemed
to enjoy the noodles I made.
I thought
you were easy to please.
I...
I was just starving.
And
maybe I
just have a good appetite.
What makes a good appetite
is not
the food,
but
who you eat with,
and how you feel.
As long as you're in a good mood,
even simple meals
can be very satisfying.
You're truly a lawyer.
You always
have a point.
Let's eat.
No talking while eating.
There's always a reason
behind the old rules.
I really like
the gift from Guan.
You know I like sculptures.
That's very thoughtful of you.
It's a professional habit.
After all,
knowing yourself and your opponent
is the key to success.
Guan is really
suitable to be a lawyer.
But
in life,
wouldn't that be too exhausting?
Sometimes,
being a bit oblivious
can be easier for a woman.
You're right.
But
I'm just afraid
that if you get used to being oblivious,
when it comes to a critical moment,
it's too late to wake up.
It's better to stay awake all the time.
At least,
I can protect the people I want to protect.
Who do you want to protect?
I don't have the ability to protect anyone now.
It's better
to protect myself first.
Do you know Su Wei?
Su Wei, the CEO?
Yes.
And Mr. Wen?
Do you know
Gu Qingyu?
No.
Mom,
what are you talking about?
You look so engaged.
Nothing much.
Just small talk.
It's getting late.
Have the driver
take Guan back.
You're not leaving tonight, are you?
Tiantian said
she'll make you breakfast tomorrow morning.
Is that true?
Yes.
I saw you didn't eat much that day,
so I thought
I could change things up for you.
Ah,
that's really thoughtful.
Alright,
then,
once you've
settled in with Guan Lu,
come find me.
I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Good night, Mr. Wen.
Mom.
Jiming,
have you really decided
to be with Guan Tiantian?
She's very capable
and can help me
and the Lin Group.
Capable?
Jiming,
you're still too naive.
Her purpose of approaching you
is not simple.
Mom,
I'm not a child anymore.
Can I decide
my own affairs?
I think you are blinded by this woman.
Look at this before you say anything.